Docker has great advantages for dotnet developers to develop run and ship their applications.
In this course, you are going to learn how to use Docker from complete starting point.
You will learn the full process of containerization, a full dotnet app.
You will also save dotnet images to talk a hub for other people to download them and use them.
And finally, deploy your dotnet apps to Azure.
And you will see how everything comes together.
This course requires no previous knowledge of Docker.
You can be a complete beginner to enroll in the scores.
After completing this course, you will have an excellent knowledge of Docker and will be ready to deploy a Docker-based dotnet apps to Azure.
These apps can be database driven and microservices.
I am super excited on this course and will teach you everything I have learned about Docker in my career.
I hope you will join me in this exciting Docker for dotnet course.